<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>GTS Assets Blog</title>
        <link>https://github.com/gts-docs/blog</link>
        <description>GTS Assets Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 05:38:11 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Introducing GTS Auto Speccer - Simplifying ROBLOX Bus Speccing]]></title>
            <link>https://github.com/gts-docs/blog/GTS Auto Speccer</link>
            <guid>https://github.com/gts-docs/blog/GTS Auto Speccer</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 05:38:11 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[GTS Auto Speccer - Enhancing Your ROBLOX Bus Speccing Experience]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="gts-auto-speccer---enhancing-your-roblox-bus-speccing-experience">GTS Auto Speccer - Enhancing Your ROBLOX Bus Speccing Experience<a href="#gts-auto-speccer---enhancing-your-roblox-bus-speccing-experience" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to GTS Auto Speccer - Enhancing Your ROBLOX Bus Speccing Experience" title="Direct link to GTS Auto Speccer - Enhancing Your ROBLOX Bus Speccing Experience">​</a></h2><p>We are excited to introduce the <strong>GTS Auto Speccer</strong>, an innovative plugin designed to streamline and accelerate ROBLOX bus speccing for your transportation projects. Whether you manage a bustling urban transit network or an intricate school bus system, the GTS Auto Speccer is here to make your vehicle customization process faster and more efficient.</p><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="features-of-gts-auto-speccer">Features of GTS Auto Speccer<a href="#features-of-gts-auto-speccer" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Features of GTS Auto Speccer" title="Direct link to Features of GTS Auto Speccer">​</a></h3><p>The GTS Auto Speccer comes packed with a plethora of features that allow you to customize the exterior of your buses effortlessly. Here are some of the key features:</p><ol><li><p><strong>Rub Rail Color Customization</strong>: Modify the Rub Rail Color (Only Huxley) to match your fleet's branding and style.</p></li><li><p><strong>Rim Colors</strong>: Choose from a wide range of Rim Colors to add a touch of elegance to your vehicles.</p></li><li><p><strong>District Name Customization</strong>: Personalize your bus by changing the District Name, making it unique to your transportation company.</p></li><li><p><strong>Light Model Changes</strong>: Transform the lighting of your buses with ease, creating distinct visual styles.</p></li><li><p><strong>Compatibility with Both Huxley and GenX</strong>: The GTS Auto Speccer works seamlessly with both Huxley and GenX bus systems.</p></li></ol><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="how-gts-auto-speccer-works">How GTS Auto Speccer Works<a href="#how-gts-auto-speccer-works" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to How GTS Auto Speccer Works" title="Direct link to How GTS Auto Speccer Works">​</a></h3><p>To get started with GTS Auto Speccer, follow these simple steps:</p><ol><li><p><strong>Opening the Plugin</strong>: Open the GTS Auto Speccer plugin from the plug-ins tab in ROBLOX Studio.</p></li><li><p><strong>Choosing the Bus System</strong>: Select the system you are using (GenX or Huxley).</p></li><li><p><strong>Selecting Your Bus Model</strong>: Click on the arrow next to "Choose Your Bus Model" and confirm your bus model.</p></li><li><p><strong>Customizing District Name</strong>: Change the District Name under the "Specifications" tab to your desired text (character limit of 60).</p></li><li><p><strong>Changing the Bus Number</strong>: Modify the Bus Number under "Specifications" to display the desired number on your bus.</p></li><li><p><strong>Customizing Ambers, Reds &amp; Taillights</strong>: Easily change the lighting setup by confirming the old and new amber/red models.</p></li><li><p><strong>Tinted Windows &amp; Black Window Frames</strong>: Check the respective checkboxes under "Specifications" for desired window options.</p></li><li><p><strong>Customizing Rim Color &amp; Material</strong>: Choose your preferred Rim Color using the Google color picker or custom part color.</p></li><li><p><strong>Changing the Rubrail Color</strong>: For Huxley buses, customize the Rubrail Color using the Google color picker.</p></li></ol><div style="width:640px;height:360px"></div><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="disclaimer-and-future-updates">Disclaimer and Future Updates<a href="#disclaimer-and-future-updates" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Disclaimer and Future Updates" title="Direct link to Disclaimer and Future Updates">​</a></h3><p><strong>DISCLAIMER</strong>: Ensure all rub rails are grouped in ONE model; otherwise, not all rub rails will change.</p><p>The GTS Auto Speccer is an early edition, and we have exciting updates planned for the future. Your feedback and suggestions are invaluable in making this plugin even more powerful and user-friendly.</p><p><a href="https://discord.gg/5k85S4KWSR" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Submit Suggestions In our Discord</a></p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="embrace-the-efficiency">Embrace the Efficiency!<a href="#embrace-the-efficiency" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Embrace the Efficiency!" title="Direct link to Embrace the Efficiency!">​</a></h2><p>With the GTS Auto Speccer, you can revolutionize your bus speccing process and spend more time focusing on your transportation projects. Enhance your fleet's appearance, set unique district names, and achieve a new level of customization!</p><p><a href="https://www.example.com/gts-auto-speccer-download" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Download GTS Auto Speccer Now</a></p><p>Join the journey with GTS Assets and create the ultimate transportation experience in ROBLOX!</p><p><img loading="lazy" alt="GTS Assets Logo" src="/gts-docs/assets/images/image1-d11d63663fb446102416697d11824d86.png" width="512" height="512" class="img_ev3q"></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>plugin</category>
            <category>speccer</category>
            <category>buses</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>